Guide to the Stanford University, Controller's Office, Cost and Management Analysis Records
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Stanford University, Controller's Office, cost and management analysis records
1976-2010
SC0869
Stanford University. Controller's Office.
11 Linear feet
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are restricted for 75 years from the date of creation.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-2007-131
  - 1985 Indirect Cost Study (tables of and figures), Mar. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1986 Indirect Cost Study, Mar. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1987 Indirect Cost Study, Mar. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1988 Indirect Cost Study, Mar. 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1989 Indirect Cost Study – Schedules, Nov. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1989 Indirect Cost Study – Summary of Assumptions (narrative), Nov. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1989 Revised Indirect Cost Study – Schedules, Jan. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1990 Indirect Cost Study – Schedules, Jan. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1990 Indirect Cost Study – Summary of Assumptions, Jan. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1991 Indirect Cost Study – Schedules, Mar. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1991 Indirect Cost Study – Summary of Assumptions (narrative), Mar. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1992 Indirect Cost Claim (narrative), 8/31/92 (1 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1992 Indirect Cost Claim (narrative), 8/31/92 (2 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1992 Indirect Cost Claim (schedules), 8/31/92 (3 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1992 Indirect Cost Claim (schedules), 8/31/92 (4 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1992 Indirect Cost Claim (appendices), 8/31/92 (5 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1992 Indirect Cost Analysis – Schedules, Jan. 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1992 Indirect Cost Analysis – Summary of Assumptions, Jan. 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1993 Indirect Cost Study – Schedules, Apr. 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1993 Indirect Cost Study – Summary of Assumptions, Apr. 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1994 Indirect Cost Study – Schedules, Mar. 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1994 Indirect Cost Study – Summary of Assumptions, Mar. 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1996 Indirect Cost Study – Schedules, Apr. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1995 & 1996 Indirect Cost Proposal, 5/30/1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1995 & 1996 Revised Indirect Cost Proposal, 1/11/1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1997 Indirect Cost Proposal, 4/30/1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1998 Indirect Cost Proposal, 11/17/1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1999 Indirect Cost Proposal, 4/8/1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 2000 Indirect Cost Proposal, 4/6/1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 2001 & 2002 Indirect Cost Proposal, 12/9/1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 2003 & 2004 Indirect Cost Proposal, 2/14/2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 2005 & 2006 Indirect Cost Proposal, 10/13/2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 2007 & 2008 Indirect Cost Proposal, 3/16/06 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1997 Staff Benefits Proposal, 3/29/1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1998 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 4/30/1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1999 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 4/2/1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 2001 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 4/20/2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 2003 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 4/24/2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 2005 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 4/22/2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Indirect Cost and Fringe Benefits Rate Agreements (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Indirect Cost and Fringe Benefits Rate Agreements (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda of Understanding Between Stanford University and the US Government [documents within date from 1979 to 1990] (1 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda of Understanding Between Stanford University and the US Government (2 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda of Understanding Between Stanford University and the US Government (3 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda of Understanding Between Stanford University and the US Government (4 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1978 Indirect Cost Proposal, May 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1980 Indirect Cost Proposal, August 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1980 Indirect Cost Study, 6/1/81 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1981 Indirect Cost Study, May 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1982 Indirect Cost Study, Dec. 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1983 Indirect Cost Study, April 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1984 Indirect Cost Proposal [no date] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1984 Indirect Cost Study, 7/23/86 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - FY2006 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 4/22/05 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - FY2007 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 5/25/06 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - FY2008 Fringe Benefits Proposal, 6/20/07 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2008-069
  - Fiscal Year 2009 and 2010 Indirect Cost Proposal (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Year 2009 Proposal for Fringe Benefits and Vacation Accrual/Disability Sick Leave (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fiscal Year 2010 Fringe Benefits and Vacation Accrual/Disability Sick Leave Proposal (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2015-158
  - Fiscal Year 2010 Incurred Fringe Benefits Costs, 2010 Dec 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Year 2011 Incurred Fringe Benefits Costs, 2012 Jan 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fiscal Year 2012 Incurred Fringe Benefits Costs, 2013 Feb 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Year 2013 Incurred Fringe Benefits Costs, 2013 Dec 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fiscal Year 2014 Incurred Fringe Benefits Costs, 2015 Feb 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fiscal Year 2016 Proposal for Fringe Benefits and Vacation Accrual/Disability Sick Leave, 2015 Apr 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)